Guys, I think I finally made it.
I think I finally made it.
But have I made it?
Isn't that saying people making fun of you?
That's when you finally make it.
It's like, you know.
Hi, Lenore.
Hi.
Hi, baby.
I don't know, I just saw.
You know, I saw some big fat black guy
making fun of Alexandra and myself and so
Maybe I'll cover that and we'll see if it's funny at all. I
Didn't think he was very funny when he was doing NorCal or
Or anybody. I don't know. He was using the troll in NorCal, maybe
Hi, is that why people were so silent or like, well, how's he gonna respond to this guy? I'll play it
It didn't seem like it was that funny to me, but I guess this is like what you guys
Or some people take this humor. Hey, but stop baby
Okay, we can we can play it. Hi. I
Don't know this guy. I mean he looks he's better than
Al Roker looks like hi, baby. Hi. What are you doing? Noor?
Hi, yeah, she's giving me a massage. Hey white dog. How are you? Yeah, she jumped up on my pack
Yeah, you give me a massage. Hey, baby
Hi
Okay, are you a parrot? Hi, baby
This is I mean, this is I did not put her up here at my shoulder. She jumped up. This is how she is
I can show you when their first when I first got her she was like this
But yeah, oh, yeah, so I got I don't know. Who's this guy? I mean I saw him on on a
Insam as before
Please for the love of God, please. Oh you want the job application? Okay?
All right only if you're McDonald's I only fill out a job applications. They're from McDonald's and
I never get the job. So I
Guess they have to yeah, I'll fill you out
Okay, I want me to hide you. You're not funny, but you know, ah, okay. There we go. So let's have a look at this
Comedy I guess this is I guess this is anybody considers comedy
Let's have a look. Okay
It got if you're if you laugh. Let me know. I don't know. It's like it's making fun of Alexandra
I don't like that and then it make you fun of me. Okay, but let's have a look not to promote this person. Oh
Excuse me. Oh
Are you showing your butthole? No, but no, no buttholes the camera
Lenore Lenore your big that's they're not very ladylike, okay?
Come on, babe
Oh, baby. Oh
I know you just kisses you just want kisses this morning, right?
You don't kisses I have I have a job, you know, I had 80 people in the chat last night
And so let's have a look at this loser. Hold on
Oh kisses you're just doing kisses this morning. Okay
Stoner scribe
But first of all his his picture doesn't look anything like him. I
Mean I think he
Okay, okay, let's have a look. Am I in the kangaroo position? Yeah, I'm at the hop with the hop
Okay, let's have a look. Let's have a look at this stand-up comedy or whatever this is
If you like what you see today consider donating down below. Every little bit helps the channel grow. Thank you so much
Hopefully nobody does
All right, everyone good morning good afternoon or good evening
Whatever time it is wherever in this vast world you may or may not happen to be
Welcome once more to another live stream of IPT Wiki Info
in conjunction with IRL News Time.
I am your hostess, Alexandra Mayers.
And I'm going to keep this brief.
I decided to go live tonight to share my opinion
and my thoughts on a certain live streamer.
I'm here, of course, to discuss a live streamer known
as Brandon Q, who I think...
Has received the forgiveness of the Lord and I think that the time has come for these IP to
affiliated communities to
Grant Brandon Q a new slate very recently a channel that I follow closely has
Entered into a little bit of a scandal by allowing Brandon Q to be part of the panel.
I'm of course referring to a live streamer known as the Cult of Psyche.
And I just want to promote the Cult of Psyche as much as possible.
I think that he is an extremely educated, insightful man.
And I think that everyone who is watching this live stream right now should go ahead and view Cult of Psyche's channel and get to know him.
Because I wholeheartedly support him and I like so many others watched his live stream with Brandon Q and I think that these IP to affiliated communities have him all wrong.
I don't think there is any evidence of Brandon Q being a pedophile.
and anything that you bring my way,
I will wholeheartedly reject it.
Like I said, a cult of psyche entered into
a significant amount of scandal
by having Brandon Q on his panel.
And my thoughts on that are that
cult of psyche is a very good person.
Extremely so.
And you know,
he's one of the people that I support.
And I consider myself to be a very good judge of character.
I like, I make sure to throw my weight in my support
behind only the best people.
For instance, I've not made any secret
about how much I support Big T, a.k.a. Controla, a.k.a. Carissa.
I've been watching many of her live streams
where she goes through her reflection journals
where she reflects on the word of God.
And I,
wholeheartedly support anyone who is a Christian. In fact, if you have, in fact, if you want nothing
to do with God, I don't really think that I want to have anything to do with you. That's just my
opinion. I'm allowed to have it. Just like how I'm allowed to have an opinion on Brandon Q, I know
that this is going to be a very controversial position. Brandon Q is a young man.
and he's a young man that likes to enjoy his youth
and maybe others, other youths.
But I don't think that he's a pedophile.
There are many in these communities
that are making these allegations and accusations on him.
And I don't think it is right to unjustly villainize someone,
especially with something as serious
as an allegation of pedophilia.
You know, I know that I,
would never falsely accuse people of pedophilia.
I would never make that kind of claim without proof.
I just think that Brandon Q is being a young,
hetero-Latino male.
And I think it's time for these communities
to give him a second chance.
Of course, I know that there have been people
that have been leaving their responses to my opinion.
Ganville.
Now Ganvel, I want to make something very clear to you. I have not watched your live streams in quite some time
I recall watching your live streams long ago in the past
and I thoroughly enjoyed masturbating to it.
That was a long time ago and I don't really remember
much of the content that you have.
I think that the only reason that you're coming after
Brandon Q is for attention.
I think you're acting out of vanity and greed.
Okay.
I don't need to watch anymore.
It's not funny.
Um, I mean, I would have laughed if it was funny. It was dumb.
I don't know, I see, you know, people that I thought, or many friends of mine, they're all having a kiki kaka kuku over, over it.
Um, I don't know, did you guys laugh? I don't know. I don't see much reaction in the chat.
Um, but I think I get the morning crowd around here either like their Kate watchers
You see you get it that runs with hate your Kate
Anyway
Did you guys laugh was it funny
He wishes he looked like Alexandra, I think he wishes he looked like her
Yeah, I mean it's like
guys
That I he does this NorCal thing. I don't know this person is but I
Don't know I think
Failed comedian. I don't know
Yeah
He looks funny
It's not it isn't really funny and it's especially, you know, I
Don't know. I didn't get the joke. Maybe
Hi
But maybe ah
Did you think it was funny you didn't laugh either did you?
Yeah, you mean kisses well, thank you bulbous, I mean I have bulbous boxing again, I mean
It is kind of like you know guys if you do come in the in the stream
It's nice to like you know say hi or something like that not just to like stare at me
We had a great show last night though, and you are missing out
If you're not watching this show because we had some great conversations last night
It was fun. We were just laughing and having a great time
I think like 80 people came in but you're missing out on it. You can go go sit on Kate's and listen to her
bitch about
whatever
And I say you can go there. I mean, it's like and you know, I'm sure you'll talk in there
You're afraid. I know your facial eat you. I
know I know
But she won't eat you. I mean, it's like I think she's full. I don't know if there's more room
for anybody else for her to eat, but you know
She can go donate more thousands of dollars more to
to Barry and Zaya and whoever she wants to you know, and then say I'm a
Protector or whatever, right? I
Don't know. I'll say what would you what should we call our predator financer?
That's what on Kate is, you know, I don't know she seems to I
Don't know maybe she's not protecting them
What happened to flirty diamond flirty diamonds around I think flirty diamonds doing her prostitution ring
In some other state and maybe keeping it on the floor the DL. Hey, Jamie. What's up girl? Good to see you
Hope you're having a good day
Yeah, but did you have fun last I had fun last night I had fun last night. I think I'm still drunk
I was doing shots of tequila and an apple juice
I had a great crowd in here last night too, great crowd.
And if you're like, you find yourself blocked in the chat,
there's a reason you're blocked in the chat,
I only block assholes.
So maybe there's some people that are blocked
and stuff like that, but I don't know, this is my take too.
There was like 20 people last stream,
not one person said hello or anything.
I mean, you can say hi, hi psyche, I mean, good morning.
Don't know. Maybe I'm still too drunk. I might be too drunk to be doing a stream right now. I don't know but uh
It was it was a fun night. It was a fun night, and I'm uh, I'm
Have some more fun nights, right?
But um
You it was fun angels demons
Oh, she went over angels and demons and she made sense in a sense of angels. Yeah, that was cool
When I got to share with her about the shem hemperage and the 72 names
You can see my I have a medallion right here
And the back of it it's called the first
There you go. There's like the 72
angels names right there
I need to give a new chain for this one, but I know that on the other side
Sorry you can see
That's called the first the first pinnacle of the Sun sorry
There you go see you got some horns you must be a capricorn he's an earth angel
Going out to find it if you get down. I'm not sure um, you know
her live
But I'm gonna I'm gonna have to look with it on her Alexander mayors channel. Oh
The North is so comfortable. Are you comfortable?
She is so comfortable right now
That is so cute
You're welcome. It might be on our Alexander mayors channel and you can go and make sure you click on the lives
Um, if it's, I don't know if it's down or not.
Uh, uh, are you, uh, here's, you're, um, you're, you're laying down, you know, this
cat is a cuddler and Rudy is a cuddler.
Is this your panther?
Yep.
Oh, there you go.
And Lola, come over here, Lola.
Lola, over here.
Come on, Lola.
Okay, come on over here.
Uh, uh.
Come on.
Hi, Lola.
Oh, you're right in front of the camera. There you go
But I'm basically in heaven when I get to call with these cats like you know
But she's so and then yeah, where's Rudy Rudy's Rudy was cuddling on in the blanket with me this morning
You like that you like that
You're spankish spanky cats like a little spankish spanky
She's so cozy though, she's like she's it's like um you can feel when they
I I gave him a wrench. I gave him a wrench. So Tommy Tommy chat 12 of me's oopy pop up. Oh, well, Tommy
Oh, Tommy James. Well, do I really care? Do I really care? I there's 80 people last night BBC for real
But you know what, how about one less person without you here?
Scram. Like, really?
At what? And that fat pussy you tell me, James?
Oh! And what is he just talking about me?
Oh, thank you as well. Oh!
Nobody cares about that fat loser.
Oh, baby, come on.
I know. Lenore's sitting on me right now.
No, sitting on top of me. Hi, babe. You want attention too? Why?
Yeah
Yeah, so I gave Patrick a rent I went back to the but the chat and I gave him a wrench. She what you're looking at
You're looking at Lenore. Hi. Hi
But I just want to say I just wanted to check in and say hi this morning
I guess like, you know, no one's in the mood. I guess cat got your tongue or something like that
All right, so I just wanted I wanted to see if that if I would find any humor and that guys
Stand up for comedy or whatever that whatever whatever he wants to call that. It was it was pretty lame
I'll be deleting the stream so I don't get a strike, but
Anyway
We should know is that you know, I don't care if there's one person in the chat
Um, as long as they're a good person rather than 50 losers. They're sure basically what's over at Tommy James. And so, you know, anyway
You have a great day
I'll be on tonight
So this is just a promo for tonight. Hey, babe. Oh, come on. Oh, she's gonna come in and oh, baby
Okay, and thank you, Jamie. Love you, Jamie
Okay, I love you. Who else commented? I love you bulbous boxing Academy
Hey, are we gonna do that a wrestling match and job application go fuck yourself and white dog?
Thanks for saying hello and
Everyone else you know
You just came here really hate watch go fuck yourself
But people that actually are just watching have a good day
And, uh, love to everybody, okay?
I'll be back all later, okay?
I'll see you soon.